originals are being activated what do i mean by originals the originals are essentially old souls
and here before done this multiple times even some from the very beginning and they're starting to
remember within this i've noticed that there are two groups the activation wave and the fresh wave
here's some signs that you might be in the activation wave of original you've done spiritual
work for years you've been through multiple dark nights of the soul you may have been rejected from
spiritual groups you may have been made to feel that you're too much or not good enough you may
have felt a little off about certain healing modalities so you just created an amalgamation
of bits and pieces of things that work for you you may struggle with naming things and attaching
certain labels to things because you understand that everything is frequency and vibration and
energy and within that there is no language you may have no desire to be right you just want peace you
probably went down lots of rabbit holes only to remember that they're also a trap you have probably
emerged from isolation which is necessary and ready to hold the frequency you've integrated your
shadow and embodied your feminine and masculine aspects you may have recently activated your actual
voice and open space in your throat may have felt isolated and confused but you would rather stay in
that state and try to force yourself back into a box who might have made several dramatic life changes
over the last couple years may now realize that you've been deliberately outcasted humiliated and
manipulated by the people closest to you in your past you may have known something was wrong with
the world since you were a child but never felt confident or strong enough to weave that into your
identity until now until now until now until now